Johnny Mad Dog is a drama, history, war film directed by Jean-Stéphane Sauvaire.
A cast of unknown performers are used in this drama about child
soldiers fighting a war in an unnamed African country.
Johnny Mad Dog, played by Christopher Minie.
Laokole, played by Daisy Victoria Vandy.
No Good Advice, played by Dagbeh Tweh.
Small Devil, played by Barry Chernoh.
Johnny Mad Dog is a 2008 Franco–Liberian war film
directed and written by Jean-Stéphane Sauvaire.
Based on the 2002 novel Johnny chien méchant by Congolese author Emmanuel Dongala, the plot follows a group of child soldiers fighting
for the Liberians United for Reconciliation and Democracy (LURD) rebels in 2003, during the Second Liberian Civil War.
The film stars Christopher Minie, Daisy Victoria Vandy, Dagbeh
Tweh, Barry Chernoh, Mohammed Sesay and Joseph Duo.
It premiered at the 2008 Cannes Film Festival.
The film explores themes of civil war, africa, child
soldier, kids, children in wartime.
The tone is emotional.